MineSweeper Tetris
MineSweeper Tetris is already running!
Please launch MineSweeper Tetris from Steam!
Steam initialization failed!
Steam current user status load failed!
MineSweeper Tetris (32-bit)
Version xxxxxxxx (Steam)
Made by ax_pokl
Licensed under GPL-3.0
OK
Initializing Steam...
Initializing Audio...
Initializing Gameboard...
Initializing Graphics...
Initializing Window...
Easy
Normal
Hard
New Game
Pause
Add Line
Help
About
Settings
Ranks
Sound
Music
Drag
Stats
Skin
Screenshot
Exit
Zoom
Animation
Cursor
On
Off
No Drag
No Number
Drag Number
Drag All
Automatic
Maximize
Bright
Dark
Minecraft
Frost
Jungle
Lava
Cumulative
Details
x1
x1.5
x2
x2.5
x3
x3.5
x4
Tutorial
Left-click a block to start game.
Number represent how many mines are in nearby blocks. Left-click another block to continue.
There is only 1 unopened block around number 1. Click number 1 to mark block as flag.
Blue grid has 1 mine and green grid has 2 mines, so red block must be mine. Right-click to mark it as question mark.
Click number 1 to open remain block, question mark will automatically marked as flag.
There are only 2 unopened blocks around number 2. Click number 2 to mark remain blocks as flags.
All mines around number 2 are marked with flags. Click number 2 to open remain blocks.
Again, click number 2 to open remain blocks.
Blue grid has 1 mine and green grid has also 1 mine, so red block must not be mine. Left-click to open it.
Mines on game board are logically unpredictable now, let's make random guess and right-click a block.
click number 2 to open remain blocks.
Oops... Due to wrong guess, 2 lines are added at top, and mines are flagged, and remain blocks are opened. Click number 1 to open remain blocks.
Click number 1 to open remain 2 blocks.
All blocks in bottom 2 lines are opened, 2 lines are cleard and 2 points are awarded. High score, high level, hard game.
New blocks are generated over time, its speed based on level. Top line is blocked until fully generated. Game over if no block can be generated.
All Mode
No Drag
No Mistake
Tetris Count
Mistake Count
Exit Tutorial?
Yes
No
Left-click regular block: open block
Left-click question block: open block
Left-click regular block: mine mark as flag
Left-click question block: mine mark as flag
Right-click regular block: mark as question
Right-click question block: unmark question
Click number: block = number, mark block as flag
Click number: flag = number, open remain block
Mark = number: open remain block, unmark question; block = number, mark block as flag
Mark = number: open remain block, mine mark as flag; flag = number, open remain block
Block is mine: add two row top, mine mark as flag
Every second: add ( level / 5 ) + 1 fix block
Fix block fill top row: fix block become clickable
All mine in row mark as flag: row clear, add 1 point
All non-mine block in row open: row clear, add 1 point
Row < 4: trigger Tetris, add 4 row, add 4 point; consecutive Tetris add 1 to 4 point
Score >= ( level + 1 ) * ( level + 1 ): level up
Easy: 12x12, 2 mine / row
Normal: 16x16, 3 mine / row
Hard: 32x24, 6 mine / row
Custom Mode
Basic Operations
Advanced Operations
Punishment and Fixed Blocks
Line Clears, Scores, and Levels
Board Size and Mine Count