MineSweeper Tetris
MineSweeper Tetris is already running!
Please launch MineSwepper Tetris from Steam!
Steam initialize failed!
Steam current user status load failed!
MineSweeper Tetris (32-bit)
Version 20221215 (Steam)
Made by ax_pokl
Licensed under GPL-3.0
OK
Initializing Steam...
Initializing Audio...
Initializing Gameboard...
Initializing Graphic...
Initializing Window...
Easy
Normal
Hard
New Game
Pause
Help
About
Settings
High score
Sound
Music
Drag Mode
Skin
Screenshot
Quit
Zoom In
Turn On
Turn Off
No Drag
Drag Number
Drag All
Automatic
Maximize
Bright
Dark
x1
x1.5
x2
x2.5
x3
x3.5
x4
Tutorial
Left-click a block to start the game
Number represent how many mines are in nearby blocks, left-click another block to continue
There is only one unopened block around number 1, click on number 1 to mark the block as a flag
Blue grid has one mine and green grid has two mines, red block must be a mine, right-click to mark as a question mark
Click on number 1 to open the rest of blocks, question marks are automatically marked as flags
Now there are only two unopened blocks around number 2, click on number 2 to flag the rest of blocks
Now all mines around number 2 are flagged, click on number 2 to open the rest of blocks
And again, click on number 2 to open the rest of blocks
Blue grid has one mine and green grid has also one mine, red block must not be a mine, left-click to open it
Mines on the game board are unpredictable now, let's make a random guess and right click a block
Click on number 2 to open the remaining blocks
Due to a wrong guess, two lines are added at top, and mines are flagged and the remaining block is opened, click number 1 to open the remaining block
Click number 1 to open the remaining two blocks
Now all blocks in the bottom two lines are opened, two lines are eliminated and two points are awarded, the higher the score, the higher the level
New blocks are generated over time, its speed depends on level, top row cannot be opened or marked until it is fully generated, when no new blocks can be generated, game is over
All Mode
No Drag
No Mistake
Tetris Count
Mistake Count
